Guide to the Records of the Office of the University Architect/Joseph J. Roberto Collection RG.11.4
New York University Archives
- Series III: Correspondence
  - Chronological File, May 1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Chronological File, Jun 1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chronological File, Jul 1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chronological File, Aug 1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chronological File, Sep 1966 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File, Oct 1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Chronological File, Nov 1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Chronological File, Jan 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Chronological File, Feb 1967 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Chronological File, Mar 1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Chronological File, Apr 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Chronological File, May 1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Chronological File, Jun 1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Chronological File, Jul 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Chronological File, Aug 1967 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Chronological File, Sep 1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Chronological File, Oct 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Chronological File, Nov 1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - By Project Number -- 1-24, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - By Project Number -- 26-69, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - By Project Number -- 70-151, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Alterations/Construction, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Alterations/Construction, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Alterations/Construction, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Alterations, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Alterations, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Alterations, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Beck, Martin, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Beck, Martin, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Beck, Martin -- Interoffice, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Beck, Martin -- Personal and Professional, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Beck, Martin -- Personal and Professional, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Beck, Martin -- Personal and Professional, Jan 1964-Jun 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Beck, Martin -- Personal and Professional, Jul 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Beck, Martin -- Personal and Professional, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Boyer, George, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Colleagues, NYU, 1961-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Kimball, Fiske, 1928-1955 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Niles, Chancellor Russell, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Niles, Chancellor Russell, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Niles, Chancellor Russell -- Correspondence with Martin Beck, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Organizations -- Civic, Cultural, Political, 1961-1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Organizations -- Italian, including Student Groups, 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Organizations -- Student, 1965-1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence -- Roberto, 1966-1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Position Applicants -- including Roberto, 1961-1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - President=s Office, 1937-1964 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Residents, Washington Square Neighborhood -- Complaints, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Roberto Personnel Material, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Robinson, Daniel D., 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - University Policy Statements and Reports, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Washington Square Association, 1966-1981 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Working Group for Alterations/Space Alterations Committee/Coordinating Group for Alterations, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Offers of Service -- Architects, A-E, 1960-1966 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Offers of Service -- Architects, F-M, 1960-1966 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Offers of Service -- Architects, N-R, 1960-1966 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Offers of Service -- Architects, S, 1960-1966 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Offers of Service -- Architects, T-V, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Offers of Service -- Architects, W-Z, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Offers of Service -- Contractors and Builders, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Offers of Service -- Consultants, Acoustical and Interiors, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Offers of Service -- Engineers, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Offers of Service -- Vendors, 1960-1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Professional organizations
  - Association of University Architects, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Association of University Architects, 1963-Apr 1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Association of University Architects -- Ninth Annual Conference at NYU, Jun 1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Association of University Architects, May 1964-Oct 1964 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Association of University Architects -- Ninth Annual Conference at NYU, Jun 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Association of University Architects, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Association of University Architects, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Association of University Architects, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Association of University Architects, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Association of University Architects, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Association of University Architects, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Association of University Architects, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Association of University Architects, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Association of University Architects, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Association of University Architects, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Association of University Architects, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - National Institute for Architectural Education, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - National Institute for Architectural Education, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Society for College and University Planning, 1967-1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Society for College and University Planning, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous -- Foreign Architects, Massachusetts, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Series V: Financial and budget files
  - Account Information, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Capital Projections, 1964-1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Capital Fund Drive, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Dormitory Authority of the State of New York -- Official Statement, Resolution on NYU Revenue Bonds, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation Brochure "Grants for Graduate Science Facilities", 1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - State of New York Report of Progress and Procedures of the Higher Education Facilities Act, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Office Budget, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Plant Funds, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Projects, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Projects, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Projects and Budgets, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Projects and Budgets, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Projects and Budgets, 1964-1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Real Estate Statements, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Space Committee Alterations, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - University Alterations, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - University Alterations, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - University Alterations, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - University Alterations, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Series VI: Progress reports
  - Project Listings, 1965-1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Progress Reports -- Construction, Design, Alterations, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Progress Reports -- Construction, Design, Alterations, Jan 1967-Jun 1967 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Progress Reports -- Construction, Design, Alterations, Jul 1967-Dec 1967 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Progress Reports -- Construction, Design, Alterations, Jan 1968-Jun 1968 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Progress Reports -- Construction, Design, Alterations, Jul 1968-Dec 1968 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Progress Reports -- Construction, Design, Alterations, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Series VII: Master planning and space allocation
  - Washington Square Center Master Plan, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square Center Master Plan -- Johnson & Foster hiring, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square Center Master Plan, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square Center Master Plan, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square Center Master Plan, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Center Master Plan -- News Clippings, 1961-1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - University Heights Center Master Plan, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Planning & Space Allocation -- University Heights [O], 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - University Heights: Planning, Space Allocation, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1964 (Box 7)
  - All Centers Planning -- Notes, ANYU Notebook@, undated, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Building Space Evaluation Reports -- Washington Sq., Univ Hts., 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Real Estate Acquisitions, Potential, 1962-1967 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Repair/Space Requests -- List, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Repair/Space Requests -- 1-20, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Repair/Space Requests -- 21-41, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Repair/Space Requests -- 45-59, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Repair/Space Requests -- 60-86, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Repair/Space Requests -- 91-151, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Space Requests, 1961-1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Building Space Analyses and Allocation -- All Centers, 1961-1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Building Space Status Reports -- Washington Square, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Building Space Status Reports -- Washington Square, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Building Space Status Reports -- Washington Square, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Building Space Analyses -- Washington Square, Univ. Heights, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Building Space Analyses -- Washington Square, Univ. Heights, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act Information on Utilization of Instructional Space -- Dean Pickett File, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Building Space Analyses -- Administrative Areas, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Building Space Analyses -- University Heights, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Allocation of University Heights Space by HEFA Categories, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Report on Classroom Utilization at Washington Square Center, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Traffic Study -- Washington Square Center, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Report on Quality Evaluation of Classrooms -- Wash Sq, Univ Hts, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Report on Quality of Classrooms at Washington Square, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Series VIII: Historic preservation and historical activities
  - Washington Square Center and Area Historical Materials, 1962-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - University Heights Historical Materials, 1961-1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Architecture of NYU Exhibition, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - NYU Sesquicentennial Committee, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Committee on the Bicentennial, 1973-Apr 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Committee on the Bicentennial, May 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Committee on the Bicentennial -- Exhibit Brochures, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Historic Preservation -- NYU Buildings, 1962-1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission Calendars -- Hearings involving NYU properties, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Commemorative Historical Plaques -- NYU Buildings, 1961-1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Historic Preservation, New York City -- Correspondence, 1967-1977 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Historic Preservation, New York City -- 20th Street Project, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Historic Preservation, New York City -- Clippings, Brochures, 1963-1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Walking Tours, New York City -- Printed Matter, 1952-1977 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Greenwich Village Walking Tour Booklet by Roberto, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission Maps -- Manhattan, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission Maps -- Bronx, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission Maps -- Brooklyn, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission Maps -- Queens, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission Maps -- Staten Island, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - New York City Landmarks -- Guidebooks, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Manhattan Landmarks -- Brochures, Flyers, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Brooklyn, Staten Island, Non-New York Landmarks -- Brochures, Flyers, Articles, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Series IX: Forms and reference materials
  - American Institute of Architects Contract Form and Articles, ca.1950-1960 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Tax Exemption Forms, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - General Conditions and Agreement, 1967-1972 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - NYU Instructions to Architects and Engineers, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - The Sanborn Map, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Successful School Planning, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Campus Buildings That Work, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Architectural Accessibility for the Disabled of College Campuses, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Building Code of the City of New York, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Building Laws of the City of New York -- Vols. 1-2 [O], 1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Building Laws of the City of New York -- Vols. 3-4 [O], 1962 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Series X: Room data sheets: Washington Square and University Heights
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 1] -- Main Building, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 2] -- Main Annex, 1962-1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol 3.] -- Brown Building, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 4] -- Waverly Building, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 5] -- East Building, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 6] -- Press Building, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 7] -- Press Annex, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 8] -- 80 Washington Square East, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 9] -- South Building, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 10] -- Education Building, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 11] -- 1-6 Washington Square North; 14A, 16 Washington Mews, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 12] -- 21 Washington Place, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 13] -- 4-6 Washington Place, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 14] -- 707 Broadway, 1963-1966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 15] -- 25 Waverly Place, 1963-1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 16] -- Commerce Building, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 17] -- Vanderbilt Hall, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 18] -- 12 University Place, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 19] -- Kimball Hall, 1964-1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 20] -- Faculty Club, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 21a] -- Warren Weaver Hall, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 21b] -- Warren Weaver Hall, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 22] -- 19 University Place, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 23] -- Barney Building, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 35] -- Faculty Club, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 36] -- South Hall, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 37] -- Gould Dormitory, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 38] -- Nichols Hall, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 39] -- Alumni Gym, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 40] -- Sage/Sage Annex, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 41] -- Havemeyer/Havemeyer Annex, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 42] -- Loew Residence Hall, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Room Data Sheets [V. 43] -- Mechanical Engineering Design Lab, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Room Data Sheets [Vol. 44] -- West Hall, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Series XI: Building files: Washington Square Center
  - American Language Institute Learning Laboratory (Proposed), 1967-1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - ANTA Theater -- Lincoln Center Repertory Theater (temporary), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - ANTA Theater -- Lincoln Center Repertory Theater (temporary), 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Barney Building, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Architect Plans Book [O], undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- News Clippings, 1961-1966 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Planning, 1952-1962 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Planning [O], 1963 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Warner, Burns, Toan, Lunde, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Warner, Burns, Toan, Lunde, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Planning, Jan 1964-Jun 1964 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Planning, Jun 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Planning, Jan 1965-Apr 1965 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Planning, May 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Grant, Loan Applications, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Planning, 1966-1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Bobst Library -- Construction Specifications: General Conditions, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Bobst Library -- Construction Specifications: 1A-5C, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Bobst Library -- Construction Specifications: 7A-14E, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Bobst Library -- Floor Plans Booklet, Directories, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Fund Raising Publications, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Drawings by Roberto, 1964-1972 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Roberto Drawings Exhibit and Sale for Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholarship Fund, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Dedication, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Signs, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Bobst/Washington Square Library -- Tenth Anniversary, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Book Center [18 Washington Place], 1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Brazilian House (Proposed), 1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Brittany Residence Hall, 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 693 Broadway, 1965-1971 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 707 Broadway, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 707 Broadway, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 707 Broadway, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 707 Broadway, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 707 Broadway, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 707 Broadway -- Alterations -- Specifications, 1962-1965 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 707 Broadway -- Alterations -- Bid Sheets, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 707 Broadway -- Admissions Office, Library, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 707 Broadway -- Bursar and Registrar Offices, 1960-1963 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 707 Broadway -- Bursar and Registrar Offices, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 707 Broadway -- Second Floor -- Bursar and Registrar Offices, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 707 Broadway -- Modern Language Association, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 707 Broadway -- Modern Language Association, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 707 Broadway -- Modern Language Association, 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 707 Broadway -- Sixth Floor, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - 707 Broadway -- Sixth Floor -- Psychology, Sociology Facilities, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - 707 Broadway -- Sixth Floor -- Psychology, Sociology Facilities, Center for Human Relations, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - 707 Broadway -- Sixth Floor -- Psychology Facilities, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - 707 Broadway -- Library Facilities, Jan 1965-Aug 1965 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - 707 Broadway -- Library Facilities, Sep 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - 707 Broadway -- Library Facilities, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - 707 Broadway -- School of Arts temporary relocation, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - 707 Broadway -- Research Center for Mental Health -- Fourth Fl., 1962 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - 707 Broadway -- Research Center for Mental Health -- Fourth Fl., Jan 1963-Sep 1963 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - 707 Broadway -- Research Center for Mental Health -- Fourth Fl., Oct 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - 707 Broadway -- Research Center for Mental Health -- Fourth Fl., Jan 1964-Mar 1964 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - 707 Broadway -- Research Center for Mental Health -- Fourth Fl., Apr 1964-Jun 1964 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - 707 Broadway -- Research Center for Mental Health -- Fourth Fl., Jul 1964-Sep 1964 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - 707 Broadway -- Research Center for Mental Health -- Fourth Fl., Oct 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - 707 Broadway -- Science Center (Proposed), 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - 715 Broadway -- Center for Safety, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 719 Broadway -- Para Education/Teacher Aide Center (ETR), 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 725 Broadway -- Cell Biology Research (Proposed), Reading Inst., 1969-1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Central Hotel Site -- Dormitory Feasibility Study, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Brown Building, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Brown Building, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Brown Building -- Tenth Floor -- Psychology Facilities, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Brown Building, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Brown Building, 1964-1966 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Brown Building -- Alterations -- Specifications, 1960-May 1962 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Brown Building -- Alterations -- Specifications, Aug 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Catholic Center -- Planning, Dedication, Fr. Andrew J. O=Reilly, 1960-1964 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Central Heating Plant, 1961-1977 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Chancellor=s Residence [34 West 11th Street], 1966-Mar 1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Chancellor=s Residence [34 West 11th Street], Apr 1967-Aug 1967 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Chancellor=s Residence [34 West 11th Street], Sep 1967-Dec 1967 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Chancellor=s Residence [34 West 11th Street] -- Sketches, Misc., undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Clocks, 1970-1981 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Commerce Building, 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Commerce Building, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Commerce Building -- Alterations--Specifications, Addition Study, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Commerce Building, 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Communications Arts Group -- Space Requirements, 1961-1964 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Computer Engineering Section, Courant Inst. -- Space Allocation, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews] -- Proposed Locations, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Drawings, Floor Plans, 1966-1970 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Finances, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 WM] -- Kirchman vs. Roberto Fees Case, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Engineering, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 WM]-- Landmarks/Historic Preservation, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 WM]-- Inspection, Occupancy Documents, 1952, 1972-1978 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 WM]-- Fire Alarm, Security, Air Condit., 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Doors, Hardware, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Construction, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Construction, Jan 1976-Oct 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Construction, Nov 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Construction, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Construction, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Specifications, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Deutsches Haus [42 WM] -- Measurements, Drawings, 1966-1977 (Box 14, Folder 20)